there was gunshots thousands of rounds of bullets from the police police moved in with tear gas and
water cannon they wanted to kill our children i had recommended to use an explosive entry device
the house shook smoke was coming in so we knew they dropped the bomb on us
police allowed the blaze to burn an hour and a half before calling in firefighters
i don't care what they said there was no justification for what they did they done
burn up two blocks explain that i never imagined that the government would drop a bomb on a row house
in philadelphia it's an embarrassment to the city of philadelphia my name is ramona africa and i was
there when the police dropped a bomb on me and my family may 13 of 1985 and killed 11 of my family
members i was there
i was there